As our trajectory continues, the massive body
of the parent planet moves directly between us
and the sun.
We are now entering the penumbra, the outer edge
of the celestial shadow. The temperature will
begin to drop rapidly as the light is obscured.
Solar efficiency will fall to critical levels.
Prepare for deep space isolation as we cross the
threshold
into total darkness.
The edge of the planet is cutting the light
A massive eclipse in the middle of the night
Temperature drops on the console screen The
coldest shadow that I've ever seen The solar
rays are starting to freeze A sudden drop by a
hundred degrees Entering the shadow, crossing
the line Losing the light, losing the sign Power
is draining, the cabin is dark Waiting in the
black for a single spark Caught in the penumbra,
cold and blind Leaving the warmth of the sun
behind A temporary death in the deep space
breeze Drifting completely on the dark space
breeze Hold your breath, and wait for the dawn
Caught in the penumbra, until the night is gone
From machinery homes with a desperate sound A
million miles from the solid ground The silence
out here has a sharper edge Like standing alone
on an icy ledge I close my eyes in the pitch black
room Swallowed alive by the planetary tomb
Entering the shadow, crossing the line Losing
the light, losing the sign The power is
draining, the cabin is dark Waiting in the black
for a single spark Caught in the penumbra, cold
and blind Leaving the warmth of the sun behind A
temporary death in the deep space breeze
Drifting completely on the dark space breeze
Hold your breath and wait for the dawn Caught in
the penumbra, until the night is gone
Just a phase of the orbit. Just a test of the
steel. The shadow is heavy. But the math is real.
Wait for the transit.
Wait for the light. Caught in the penumbra Cold
and blind Leaving the warmth of the sun behind A
temporary death in the deep space freeze
Drifting completely on the dark space freeze
Hold your breath And wait for the dawn Caught in
the penumbra Until the night is gone
Wait for the dawn.
The solar rays are dark
in the penumbra.